tierra.net 2018-09-22

# 

**Overview**

This Privacy Policy describes how and when TierraNet Inc. (“ **we** ” or “ **us** ”) collects, uses and shares your personal information (or personal data) when you visit our website or use any of our Services. Our Services and website are intended for use by those 18 years and older.

If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy (this “ **Policy** ”), please do not use this website or disclose information to us. 

We reserve the right to modify all or any portion of this Policy at any time. We will provide notification of changes to this Policy via this website at least 30 days before the changes take effect. In some cases, we may email notice of the changes to you. You are responsible for reviewing this website periodically to ensure you are aware of modifications to this Policy. Changes we make to this Policy will not apply retroactively.

**Information Collection and Use**

We collect information from you when you visit our website, send us an email, use our chat support, or call us by telephone. We collect information to provide you service and process payments. We may collect personally identifiable information you voluntarily provide to us such as your first and last name, address, email address, phone number, payment information (such as credit/debit card number). In addition we may collect information automatically when you visit our website such as IP address, web browser, and operating system.

**Third Party Services**

When you visit this website, we reserve the right to use third party services such as Google Analytics. By doing so, we may gather information such as the date and time of your visit, the pages of this website you visit, the address of the website you visit immediately prior to visiting this website, and the type of browser and operating system you use to access this website.

**Cookies**

This website uses cookies to collect information about how you use this website. A “cookie” is a small text file sent from this website to your web browser. You can choose not to receive a cookie by enabling your browser to either refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. However, some portions of this website or our services may not function properly if you disable cookies.

**Correspondence**

We may contact you via any personally identifiable information you provide to us. For example, we may email you to market our Services.

**Sharing Personally Identifiable Information**

We may share the information you disclose to us. Within our company, we limit access of this information to authorized individuals who have a need to know and who have signed confidentiality agreements with us or are under a legal obligation of confidentiality. We may also disclose such information to trusted third parties who work with us on this website, or who provide marketing, product development, and other services to us, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Parties we share information may include: Payment Processors, Fraud Prevention Providers, Registry Operators, ICANN, and SSL Certificate Issuers.

**Releasing Information**

We reserve the right to release your personally identifiable information if required by law. This includes, but is not limited to, responding to subpoenas, search warrants , court orders and other judicial and administrative requirements. We may also release your personally identifiable information if we have a good faith belief such action is necessary to protect this website or other rights.

**Business Transfer**

In the event of our merger, acquisition, sale or transfer of assets or equity to another company, your personally identifiable information may be transferred as part of that transaction.

**Modifying Or Deleting Your Information**

To view and update your personally identifiable information, please log-in to your account by clicking the “Login” button at the top of the homepage and then go to “Control Panel”. You may also modify the information by contacting us using the Contact Us information below.

We will retain personal information for a minimum of 2 years following termination of services unless you explicitly request that we delete your personal information.

You may request that we delete your personal information to the extent it is no longer in use, required by law or contractual compliance. You may request that your information be deleted by contacting legal@tierra.net.

**Security Precautions**

We employ reasonable security procedures and practices to maintain the safety of your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number, we encrypt the transmission of that information using Secure Sockets Layer technology (SSL).

Transmitting information via the Internet is never completely secure. Therefore, you should understand that any information submitted may be intercepted by others. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you send to us through email or this website, and you do so at your own risk. If you do not feel comfortable providing information through email or this website, please call our office directly using the contact information below.

**Links to Third Party Website**

This website may include links to third party websites. These third party websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We have no control, responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of this website and welcome any feedback about any third party websites accessed through these links.

**Governing Law**

This website is controlled, operated and administered entirely within the United States. This Policy and the use of this website are governed by California law without giving effect to its principles of conflict of laws.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at:

Attn: Legal Dept.

TierraNet Inc.

P.O. Box 502010

San Diego, CA 92150-2010

or by email:

legal@tierra.net
